Longing for miracles that can inspire Awaken, returner
But your heart-filled desire Excitement, take joy wherever you can
Give it to me!
My name's Mai-Mai Yuzariha. I'm a second year in high school.
And yes, I am aware that Mai-Mai is an unusual name.
I broke them again.
That's okay. Now they're kaleidoscopes.
Anyway, it's time for me to go to the public bath.
I always look forward to that nice hot water.
Afternoon!
Let's see, the women's bath is that way.
The bath is great, but the real treat is that yummy fruit milk I get to drink right after!
Freshman, here I go!
Gah!
This day benigny
Make sure monge
Make sure that my boy
Fight me
of a
Guess what, everyone?
We got a new member.
Huh?
Give it up for Franshu Shus number seven.
Can't hear you!
I'm sorry, sir. I don't understand.
You really need me to spill it out for you!
You went to the public bath because ours is broken, right?
And you came back with what I hope isn't a dead body.
Oh, the zombies have a problem with corpses now?
So she is dead?
You should take a look at yourselves before you throw around the D-word, babe.
That's not an answer!
Shh! Hey, it's cool!
After all, what's one more zombie to add to the idle army of the dead?
Aw, crap. This is bad.
Where exactly did you find her?
Hmm? What did you say? Something dumb?
Come now, I didn't find her, per se.
It's more like the universe guided me to her.
How's that?
How should I know?
We've been to temples and shrines all over Saga!
Maybe I pissed off some ancient god!
Whoa, Shades, did you...
No, I'm innocent!
I didn't do squats!
You've got red on you.
Then how did...
You gotta believe me!
Oh, no, no, it's heading right to our bodies don't move on their own!
No, no, no, it's heading right to our bodies don't move on their own!
Says the zombie!
But I thought it was only us!
Hey, do you think you could maybe tell us whether you're dead or not?
Oh my gosh, did I die?
Huh?
I can't believe you didn't check to make sure!
You might not be a murderer, but this means that you've abducted a high school student.
You think she knows that we're zombies yet?
Looks that way.
I mean, she's staring into your lack of a soul, Sakura.
Uh, that's not good, but at least she hasn't figured out that we're Frans Shushu.
Are you Frans Shushu's number one?
That's right!
I knew she looked familiar.
She comes to see our shows all the time.
You're that girl with the glasses who's always in the crowd!
I would have recognized you anywhere.
I am a giant fan of your work.
I never would have known that you guys were all zombies, though.
And Pop goes the C-word.
Well, I guess this is it.
It was fun while it lasted.
So now what do we do?
There's only one thing to do.
We'll just have to kill her.
Though I suppose there's a less bloody solution.
Oh, please don't worry.
I mean, you guys do look pretty sickly and banged up right now.
But during a show, nobody would ever notice you're not alive.
You always look so cute and beautiful when you're performing.
Is that all just makeup?
She's taking this like a champ.
Maybe zombies just aren't all that shocking anymore.
Except you got shot.
Only like two times.
Hey, so about the whole secretly undead idols thing.
Could you, uh...
Huh?
Please not tell anyone!
I'm begging you!
Come on!
Grovel already!
Ka-ching!
There is an obvious fix for this.
You guys should let me be a part of Ron Shushu.
Huh?
It'll be way easier to keep the secret if I'm in the group, right?
What do you mean?
My, aren't you a bold one.
Come on, please!
Ha-ha!
Huh?
That was easy.
You didn't think this through for a second, did you?
You can't just let her win, man!
Ha-ha!
Thank you very much.
I promise I'll give it my best.
You can call me Mai Mai Yuzuriha.
And yeah, that is actually my real name.
Uh, okay, Mai Mai.
Sounds like something you would name a puppy.
Well, it's almost curfew for me.
See you tomorrow.
Bye!
So she's gonna commute instead of staying here.
That's an option?
What the hell?
Ha-ha!
Ugh!
Hey, Mai Mai!
Let's go get some frozen tapioca!
Sorry.
I'll have to say tapinoka.
Aw, man.
I didn't know you had festival stuff today.
Actually, it's something way cooler than the festival.
Wait, if Mai Mai's bailing on tapioca, then...
Hold on!
Do you have a hot date or something?
Tell us now!
Not in the romantic sense.
But it is a crucial rendezvous.
Good morning, girls!
Mai Mai reporting in!
Are you dead serious about becoming an idol?
That's the grave!
And you may know our secret,
but you can't use that against us.
I wouldn't dare.
Fair enough.
So Mai Mai, do you have any dance experience?
Nope, afraid I will be starting off at zero.
But I do have all of the lyrics and routines
memorized from all of your shows and CDs!
Are you serious?
That's so incredible!
Five, four, three, two, one!
Now begin!
Two, three, four, five, six, ready, pose!
Why are you a pretzel?
I can do it perfectly in my head,
but my body is not quite there yet.
Look, Sakura!
She's gonna break her neck and end up like us!
I'm not positive Mai Mai can handle this.
Let's try again.
Bowie!
And fight!
It's not broken!
One more time.
And again!
No!
Again?
Hail!
That's enough.
Let's call it a day for now.
I don't want to stop.
I want to be a real member of Fron Shushu
as soon as possible!
Make sure to practice what we did today, okay?
Right-o!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Dude.
You're kidding me!
It's in color!
Sakura!
Look!
This thing's in color!
Oh yeah, that is cool!
Does it have Oya Jichi?
Yeah, he's there.
It's the 20th anniversary edition!
Wicked!
I'd be pissed if he wasn't!
Love that guy.
You worked really hard today.
I've got a lot to learn.
You impressed Ai with the energy you brought.
I just want everyone to accept me.
So how long have you been a Fron Shushu superfan?
Well, I was beginning to give up on Saga.
Huh?
And then I realized, this place has a lot of potential.
But nobody knows that.
Guess that's just part of Saga's thing, I figure.
Like if Saga were Fukuoka, everyone would think of it as a lively place with active residents,
and then people would probably care about it a whole lot more.
Yeah, Saga is kind of its own thing.
Anyway, one day I was flipping through Saga's zine,
and I was like,
Whoa!
Idols in Saga?
I saw that you were doing a show at the end of the year.
You liked it that much?
It was totally mind-blowing!
Oh gosh, thank you.
I don't know how to say it,
but I'm amazed at your expression whenever you sing.
The way you're able to shine so brightly.
It got me thinking more and more about how I wanted to be just like you
and live a super cool life in Saga,
the same way you and your friends do.
You are just like me.
But the EFS show was a real mess.
Trust me, we felt it in the crowd, too.
I have never wished that I could make my voice ring out louder than I did that day watching my faves up on that stage.
But when you played Saga Arena,
I realized how amazing you guys truly are!
You may be zombies,
but you're just as alive as anyone!
So I don't think you need to worry too much about makeup and superficial stuff like that.
Because being able to perform the way you do is loads more special!
I know that I can't contribute much yet,
but I am willing to do whatever I can for Fron Shushu!
We'll work hard together.
Yeah!
We're pathetic!
We put all our heads together and this is the best we can do?
Let's just go with the beauty pageant again and be done with it.
But that's a cop-out!
Not that any of these plans are better!
Can't we ink out one decent idea?
A school festival show?
If we get popular with high school students,
it'll really help with visibility!
The grounds will be so crazy!
Trust me!
Yeah!
Shushu!
See?
Yeah!
Shushu!
High schoolers, huh?
So look fun!
A worthwhile endeavor, I would say.
What do you think?
Wipe that stupid smile off, or I will!
The crowd you girls tend to attract
is a hodgepodge of losers and freaks.
Let's take aim at the demographic
that'll shape Saga's future.
Kay, what about Mai Mai?
She can't get through a routine without hurting herself.
Then get it together quick,
cause she's the star.
This concert marks the rebirth of Fron Shushu
as a group of eight,
and the debut of number seven!
Do you think you're ready for this?
As long as my body doesn't betray me, yes?
Then all you gotta do is practice your butt off
until the show.
Now, let me see your game face!
Okay!
Come on, mind and body,
please be in sync for once!
The new Fron Shushu is gonna rock all their socks off!
Yeah!
Great!
You've got it!
Awesome!
I see you've managed to remain upright this time.
Two days till the show.
That was close!
Thanks for supporting me!
Hey!
This calls for a group outing!
Let's hit the public bath!
It's kinda my thing.
I know some great spots...
I hate to say it, Mai Mai,
but we're gonna have to pass on that one.
Uh-uh.
Not that we don't like baths.
But they're kinda a dead giveaway.
Oh my gosh!
I'm so sorry!
I forgot!
It's fine!
Actually, it might be fun to go
and check out your school instead!
Nice!
That way we can take over their turf!
Whoa!
I don't have a lot of memories from high school, actually.
Yeah, neither do I.
I'd be interested to see how the young people of today
spin their youth.
Great!
Let's do it!
I can get permission from my teacher!
Oh, boy!
Hurry up!
The festival's tomorrow!
That was such a drag, right?
I'm sorry.
The others kind of took off.
No worries!
Everyone's pumped about the cultural festival tomorrow,
so they are sure to run into excited students wherever they go.
You're right.
The prep always was half the fun.
So, what were you like in your high school days, Sakura?
Hmm.
Kinda dead on the inside.
Well, you see, some disappointing stuff happened.
So I had trouble taking anything seriously.
Are you saying that you'd lost all hope?
Mm-hmm.
But then I saw Iron Frill.
And I was so inspired by I and the rest of the group
that I built up the strength to keep moving forward.
Around that time, you could always find me practicing
in a corner of the classroom.
So I was super happy when I found out
they were auditioning new members.
But then I died before I got to apply.
Being a zombie isn't all bad, though,
because now I get another chance.
After meeting the rest of the group,
I feel like I can take on any challenge,
even an EFS do-over show.
Huh?
Huh? Wait, what?
You're going back?
Nobody told you that?
Definitely not.
That was a catastrophe for you, remember?
Why would you want to do that to yourself again?
That's who Fran Shushu is.
Look, I know.
EFS was a total mistake.
We ended up in debt,
and we couldn't even do idle stuff
for a pretty long time.
But still,
none of us gave up.
Sure, it's scary to think
something like that could happen again,
but if we're together,
we can face anything.
And I mean,
if we ever gave up trying,
that'd be worse.
We'd be wandering lost
with the rest of the dead.
our hearts may not beat anymore,
but we're still living
because we refuse to quit chasing our dreams.
We keep rising from the ashes.
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry!
They came out really corny
and kind of conceited, huh?
What's the matter?
So that's who Fran Shushu is.
Yeah, and now that we have you
as a part of the group,
we're even stronger.
Let's make sure that we put on
an amazing show tomorrow, okay?
That's who Fran Shushu's number one is.
Hey, are you okay there, Mai Mai?
I think maybe you missed the point
of my entire speech.
Hang on a sec!
Did you forget something?
You know, me?
My, Mai, don't worry.
You've practiced hard for this show.
Yeah, sweet!
Let's get out there and rock!
Right!
Here we go!
I'm excited!
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
we're just gonna go
Huh? Who's that?
Hey, you've got a new member.
Yes!
Wow!
Is that Mai Mai?
What is happening?
Ah,前髪,
切りすぎ
だけど
君が
君を
連れて
ね
帰って
ありって
おもみ
ちっくり
近づく
散臭
だぞ
泥どえな
今日を
ちっくり
もっと
今から
勝負
ずっと
突撃
狂う
ライト
乙女座
はラッキー
じゃん
引き進む
ハッピーデイ
エイ
キップ
ジャンク
三角
こんじゃ
トキメキ
止まらない
デリバーで
ライト
スター
アイ
ハッピーパー
ゴールデータイ
エイ
おごりでしょ
クレープ
カトナ
まとめて
NOW IS FOREVER
HEY
アッチャ
KEY
BABY
HEY
METCH
SHAVE
I
HEY
まとめざわランキーチャー
A-LOW ART
C-C-HAPPY DAY
A-B-C-C
キップ
ジャンク
三角
こんじゃ
トキメキ
止まらない
踊りバーで
レッツダースター
I-I-P-I
H-I
D-E-N-K-I
F-Y-P-I
踊りでしょ
クレープ
カトナ
まとめて
we me
have
Q
A
X
あ
たこ
イ
いただいた
ハイ
メナ
eins
ハイ
verd
We officially have a new member!
Hello! My name is Number Seven!
It's nice to meet you all!
She's an idol now!
Dang, that came out of nowhere!
This lot sure keeps you on your toes!
Listen to what Seven has to say!
Knock him dead, newbie!
First and foremost, I want to thank each and every one of you
for coming to the Saganon Carnival today!
It really means the world to us!
And now, if you all don't mind,
I have one more announcement!
You see, after today's show is over,
I will be graduating!
Leaving Franz Shushu!
And now, I hope you'll enjoy
Into the Light, my last song!
Thank you!
mouths to get ready
和, love, love, keep you
dragged over, now!
今旅立ちます
瞼閉じれば
溢れる思い出
I've been thinking about it a lot ever since I had that talk with Sakura yesterday.
And my mind's made up.
I thought I was the same as you guys despite being alive but I was wrong.
It's not your cold skin or lack of heartbeat either.
None of you were alive for very long but I think each of you lived out your short lives with everything you had.
The reason you shine so bright is because even after dying you keep rising again.
It's like you're dead set on living your afterlife to the fullest.
I think if I want to shine like that, the first step is making the most of my life here in Saga.
That's why I'm gonna graduate from Franz Shushu and live here and now in the Reiwa era.
Okay, that was all I wanted to say. And with that, adieu!
Sayonara,またね!
Atatakai Memories!
You've got a ton of amazing qualities. You came through like a storm.
Yeah, your name might as well be bye-bye.
Don't ever forget the courage that brought you this far.
It has been such an honor to share this stage with you.
Look us up when you croak for real, Kay!
Kay!
Oh, this is for you!
But I can't take this, it's way too fancy!
It's fine, I insist!
Oh, okay. Thank you! I swear I'll protect it!
We weren't together for long, but it was so great to have you in Franz Shushu.
We'll never forget you, promise.
Yeah, same here!
I'm sorry.
Oh no! This entire whirlwind happened because of a mix-up I caused.
And it led me on an incredible adventure.
I see.
Don't worry, I will keep everything a secret as long as I live.
I mean, I would want to lose my heroes after all.
Thanks for that.
I keep coming to the same conclusion.
I can't find any information on number five, but as for the rest of Franz Shushu...
Saki Nikaido, Ai Mizuno, Junko Kono, Lily Hoshikawa, Tai Yamada, and Sakura Minamoto.
No doubt about it, all those girls are dead.
This is Yugiri.
No matter the era, the hearts of young people are always filled with passion.
Zombieland Saga Revenge, Episode 8, The Saga Incident, Part 1.
Apologies for the wait.
Have a great!
Top 7
seinen characters
To adultery
aba
將
abbiamo
Inanna
Be with
la
었던
M
off